Finding Aid for the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California Records LSC.0900
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1950s-1970s
  - Blefare & Michel v. U.S. Ca 9 #19825 -- David L. Mundt (Box 1039)
  - Out of Town - prisoner correspondence. Contreras, Suzy. Dalton, Nancy. (Box 1040)
  - Annie Krachun. Mundt, Davud L. Anagnos - May. (Box 1041)
  - Anagnos v. FBI -- Adams v. Superior Court (jury selection 7/73), 1973, n.d. (Box 1042)
  - Anagos v. CIA, Anagos v. Colby FBI, n.d. (Box 1043)
  - Anagnos v. CIA. Carr, Mary Virginia C.P.L.S., n.d. (Box 1044)
  - Carr, Mary Virginia., n.d. (Box 1045)
  - Abbott v. County of LA. ACLU vs. Procunier - distribution of "On the Line" at Soledad., 1971, n.d. (Box 1046)
  - Armas, Able- notes. Lt. Armas v. Board of Police & Ed Davis., n.d. (Box 1047)
  - Lt. Armas v. Board of POlice and Ed Davis -- Bradley v. Judges (jury selectioon case) (Box 1048)
  - Bryan v. Azusa Pacific College Inc. Calif. Newspaper Publishers Assn. v. Burbank, n.d. (Box 1049)
  - Calif. Newspaper Publishers Assn. v. Burbank. Canarillo. Cannon v. Davis., 1976, n.d. (Box 1050)
  - Cannon v. Davis, n.d. (Box 1051)
  - Cannon v. Davis., n.d. (Box 1052)
  - Cannon materials, n.d. (Box 1053)
  - Cannon v. Davis. Ar. v. City of LA. Cherry v. Arnett. Christiansen v. Kelley., n.d. (Box 1054)
  - Castille v. Dept of Water and Power. Castille v. DWP. Davis b. Johnston. Diversified services- criminal libel. (Box 1055)
  - De Vries v. Acree. Diversified publications v. Davis. Farr., n.d. (Box 1056)
  - Ferguson v. Griggs. Fernandez, Joe v. Santa Barbara High School District. Fiske v. Bd. of Education., 1976, n.d. (Box 1057)
  - Fiske, Fiske v. Board of Education, n.d. (Box 1058)
  - Fiske v. Bd. of Ed. Fiske, Susanne v, Santa Barbara Coast Youth Fooball League, 1975, n.d. (Box 1059)
  - Fiske v. Bd. of Ed. Fonda, Jane v. Nixon. (Box 1060)
  - Fonda v. Nixon - pleadings, caption sheets, summary, correspondence. (Box 1061)
  - Fiske v. Board of Ed., Fluoride. Four-Star Theatre. Gendron b. Richardson. Grossman, Aubry. (Box 1062)
  - DeWayne Hall v. Moffett. Hamling, U.S., v. Hannon v. Davis. Henkel v. Mattern. Henry v. Warner., n.d. (Box 1063)
  - Henry v. Warner as Secretary of Navy. Daniel Edward Henry et al. v. Hon John E. Warner, et al. Hixon, Larry. Homemakers v. Dept of Industrial Relations. (Box 1064)
  - Howard, G. v. Bd. of Governers in Calif. Community Colleges -- McClay Junior High School., 1975, 1977, n.d. (Box 1065)
  - Chronological 1974 materials. McZeal. May v. CIA., 1974, n.d. (Box 1066)
  - Michaelson, Alvin S. Moss, Dr. Penrod v. LA Bd. of Ed. Peo v. Muer. Muer, Peo., n.d. (Box 1067)
  - People v. Muer. Peo. v Muer. Nieman, Robt, A., n.d. (Box 1068)
  - Nude bathing in Laguna Beach -- Rock v. Secretary, Dept of Defense., n.d. (Box 1069)
  - Rock & roll festival, in re Ricketts, Sparrow v. Goodman, St. James & Jonston, Peo v. San Fernando Valley State College. (Box 1070)
  - SFVSC. Mickey - habeus corpus - Calif. S. Ct., 1971, n.d. (Box 1071)
  - Mickey v. Calif. Chatman appeal. SFVCS., 1969, n.d. (Box 1072)
  - SFVSC-- Valley State App. Dept., 1969, n.d. (Box 1073)
  - Martin, Bonnie Lee -- Bell, Howard B., n.d. (Box 1074)
  - Brantley, Michael -- Kaumo, Karl., n.d. (Box 1075)
  - Blumberg, H.H. --Weinstein, A., n.d. (Box 1076)
  - Sepulveda, Reuben -- Holland, James. (Box 1077)
  - Grant, Jerry -- Schoenthal, Jann, n.d. (Box 1078)
  - Wilson, David -- Roberts, Aaron (Box 1079)
  - Seal Beach dog & cat ordinance; Singer, Stuart P. Peo v.; Subscription TV v. So. Calif. Theatre Owners Assn.; St. Ledger v. Deering, n.d. (Box 1080)
  - Stone v. Powell. Shulford. Taylor, Glenn T. v. State Personnel Bd. Torres, Art v. Chamberlain., n.d. (Box 1080)
  - Tepper & Marxhall v. Co. of LA.; Tipton v. Calif Unemployment Insurance Appeals Bd.; Janet Weathers v. Superior Ct.; Women's Parade; Yorty v. Chandler; Zebra- round up of Blacks, 1975, n.d. (Box 1081)
  - Board of Directors -- Prisons., 1982- 1987, n.d. (Box 1082)
  - Public Affairs -- ACLU Execs, 1986-1987, n.d. (Box 1083)
  - Public Affairs -- Crew Position Paper, n.d. (Box 1083)
  - No On One Campaign Committee Papers, Herald Dispatch, Valley News, Northeast Newspapers, Herald Examiner, LA Times, ACLU Task Force, List of Volunteers, n.d. (Box 1084)
  - Names & Organizations to add to Endorsement List, C.A.P. One Event, Media, Bills (Box 1084)
  - Robbins Amendment -- Receipts (Box 1085)
  - No On One Press Conference, Correspondence, Robbins Amendment Copies, Contact California, Info & Thank Yous, Literature (Box 1086)
  - Meeting Minutes, Organizations, Literature, n.d. (Box 1086)
  - Names to be Added to Mailing List, n.d. (Box 1087)
  - No On One - Fundraisers, Speakers Bureau, Letters of Support, Request For Speakers, Lawyers Statement, Capone Working Papers (Box 1087)
  - Tinsley, n.d. (Box 1088)
  - El Centro, n.d. (Box 1089)
  - Koehler, n.d. (Box 1090)
  - Harvey Karman, n.d. (Box 1091)
  - Jerome Weber, Fonda FBI File (Box 1092)
  - Secret Service- Fonda, Motion For Emergency Inj., Ex Parte Application, Order TSC, Newsclippings, 3/18/76, n.d. (Box 1093)
  - Duak. Robles, n.d. (Box 1094)
  - Robles. Aznavorian., n.d. (Box 1095)
  - Herbert, n.d. (Box 1096)
  - Jones- Pretrial Confinement, n.d. (Box 1097)
  - Will Lewis- correspondence, related cases (Box 1098)
  - Lewis, ACLU - KPFK- Grand Subpoenas- Materials and extra copies, 7/31/74 (Box 1099)
  - Draft environmental impact report, Storer et al. vs. Brown, n.d. (Box 1100)
  - Special Education, Seattle Briefs, n.d. (Box 1101)
  - Savala, n.d. (Box 1102)
  - El Centro, n.d. (Box 1103)
  - El Centro, n.d. (Box 1104)
  - Garcia - PCL, n.d. (Box 1105)
  - SWP, n.d. (Box 1106)
  - Defense, NSA, Fonda Materials and Summaries, Smith- FBI (Box 1107)
  - State, Dean, Mardian, P Fonda's Ints., to Fed, Defts., Motion to Compel Kelley (Box 1108)
  - Cointelpro, Fonda- related cases, Nixon Litigation, Fedl. Defts.' Disc. v. Fonda, Post Office (Box 1109)
  - FBI Docs- FOIA, FBI Files, Erlichman, Haldeman, Colson, n.d. (Box 1110)
  - Jaffe, Fonda's Ans to Ints., request for Docs, Correspondence, Wiretap - Dellinger Order, Kelley- Discovery (Box 1111)
  - Customs, Extras, Marlene's Synopsis of Exceptions, Public Records Act/Information Act, Notes, Info on Health Centers, Shepard's Citations for Black Panther's, Fem Women's Health Centers v. Dept of Health, n.d. (Box 1112)
  - New West Magazine -- ACLU v. Deukmejian Casey, n.d. (Box 1113)
  - Fem. Wom. Health Centers v. Dept. of Health and B. Myers. Hubert v. Williams (Box 1114)
  - Mel Roberts, John S. Rodell, Steve Padella, Rodriquez, J Clark Pleadings, Clark w,. Brown, Review Board, 1981, n.d. (Box 1115)
  - J Clark Pleadings 1980 etc., Clark v. Brown Pleadings Pre-1980, Clark v. Brown Chronological Correspondence 1979-1981 (Box 1116)
  - Pleadings Vol 1, Extra Copies of Pleadings, Memorandum Kensey Institute Study Drafts, Correspondence, Walter Arthur Richards, Richards v. Richards (Box 1117)
  - Laurie Kell v. Peter Pitchess, Margaret Nagle McCourtney v. Cory, Parents &Friends/Gays v. Az. Correction Facility (Box 1118)
  - Correspondence, Sanchez Divorce Papers -- Jones v. Daly (Box 1119)
  - Schmidt, et al. v. North O.C. Comm. College District Trustees, n.d. (Box 1120)
  - ACLU- San Diego Chapter, Counsel 1/1/79 - 12/31/80 (Box 1121)
  - Counsel, National ACLU Correspondence 1962- 1970 (Box 1122)
  - Aguiluz, Heroico M -- Cota, J. Alex, n.d. (Box 1123)
  - Cotton & Bregman, Davidson. R.F. Peo v. (Box 1124)
  - Davis v. County of LA -- Finder v. General Telephone (Box 1125)
  - Fox -- Hopgood: Rehab, Civil Service, APL, n.d. (Box 1126)
  - Heffron v. Iskcon -- Looker v. City of Santa Barbara, n.d. (Box 1127)
  - Levin -- Roberts, Greg, n.d. (Box 1128)
  - Reyes v. Santa Ana USD -- Souter, People v., n.d. (Box 1129)
  - Schmidt, Karen v. No. OC Comm. Dist. Bd. of Trustees -- Whitmore v. County of L.A., n.d. (Box 1130)
  - Bagstad v. Orange County Transit Dist., n.d. (Box 1131)
  - ACLU Foundation Correspondence 1975-1980, Statistics and Reports. American Bookseller Ass., Inc. (Box 1132)
  - Blake v. City of LA, California Teachers Ass. and ACLU v. Riles (Box 1133)
  - CTA v. Riles, Burton v. Pasadena City Bd. of Education, n.d. (Box 1134)
  - Blake v. City of LA, #2,3, n.d. (Box 1136)
  - Medical Complaint Center Vol. 1, 2. Lopez v. Pomona Plumbers Union, n.d. (Box 1137)
  - Nicholson v. Bd. of Ed., Torrance School District. -- Melvin v. Bd. of Supervisors, n.d. (Box 1138)
  - Nicholson v. Bd. of Ed., n.d. (Box 1139)
  - LA Main File #1, 2, 1949- 1964, 6/26/30- 4/29/55 (Box 1140)
  - LA Main File #3- 6, 8, 5/31/55 - 10/12/60 (Box 1141)
  - LA Main File #7, 9, 10, 2/1/60 - 11/6/63 (Box 1142)
  - LA Main File #11, 12, 20- 22, 11/26/63 - 7/3/75 (Box 1143)
  - LA Main File #13- 16, 19, 10/66- 3/21/77 (Box 1144)
  - La Main File #23, 24, 1949-1968 (Box 1145)
  - LA Main File #17, 18, 26, 4/8/71- 10/26/72 (Box 1146)
- Briefs
  - Fernandez v. Hartman, etc. (Box 1147)
  - Garcia v. Landon, etc. (Box 1148)
  - Oil Workers v. Superior Ct., etc., n.d. (Box 1149)
  - Black v. Cutter Laboratories, etc., n.d. (Box 1150)
  - Newcomb v. USA, etc., n.d. (Box 1151)
  - Stainback v. Po, etc., n.d. (Box 1153)
  - Acheson v. Kuniyuki, etc., n.d. (Box 1152)
  - Briefs, Administrative Law- Cases and Comments. (Box 1154)
  - Briefs, Who's Who in American Education Vol. XIV, 1949-50, n.d. (Box 1155)
  - Briefs, Lawyers Guild Review Vol. 14-16, 1954-56, n.d. (Box 1156)
  - Edwards v. USA, etc., n.d. (Box 1157)
  - Briefs, Obscene Literature and Constitutional Law (Box 1158)
  - Cohen vs. Cahill, etc., n.d. (Box 1159)
  - Rodd v. USA, etc., n.d. (Box 1160)
  - ILWU v. Boyd, etc., n.d. (Box 1161)
  - Hirschman v. County of LA, etc., n.d. (Box 1162)
  - Amaya v. US, etc., n.d. (Box 1163)
  - Marshall and Delmonico v. United States, etc. (Box 1164)
  - Steinmetz, etc., n.d. (Box 1165)
  - Wheeldin v. US, n.d. (Box 1166)
  - Briefs, Lawyers Guild Review Vol. 12-13, 1952-1953, n.d. (Box 1167)
  - Briefs, Lawyers Guild Review Vol. 1-7, 1941-1947, n.d. (Box 1168)
  - Brown & Albert v. OSHIRO, etc., n.d. (Box 1169)
  - Briefs, Lawyers Guild Review Vol. 8-11, 1948-1951, n.d. (Box 1170)
  - Grunwald - Marx v. LA Joint Board, etc., n.d. (Box 1171)
  - Orange Coast Jr. College v. St John, etc. (Box 1172)
  - McClain v. Budzislawski v. Jones, etc., n.d. (Box 1173)
  - Briefs, Carbo v. US Section 2255 Proceedings, n.d. (Box 1174)
  - Briefs, Lawyers Guild Review Vol. 17-18, 1957-1958, n.d. (Box 1175)
  - George v. USA, etc., n.d. (Box 1176)